A lesson in terror.
Night School is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Ken Hughes.
A Boston police detective investigates a series of gruesome decapitations of various
college coeds, committed by a helmeted, black-leather clad serial killer.
Lt. Judd Austin, played by Leonard Mann.
Eleanor Adjai, played by Rachel Ward.
Vincent Millett, played by Drew Snyder.
Taj, played by Joseph R. Sicari.
Gus, played by Nicholas Cairis.
Carol, played by Karen MacDonald.
Night School (also released as Terror Eyes) is a 1981 American slasher film directed
by Ken Hughes and starring Rachel Ward, Leonard Mann, and Drew Snyder.
The plot follows a series of brutal decapitation murders occurring
around a women's night college in Boston, Massachusetts.
It marked the debut feature film of Ward, and the final film directed by Hughes.
The music score was composed by Brad Fiedel.
Filmed on location in Boston's Beacon Hill neighborhood, Night School premiered in January 1981 at the Avoriaz International
Fantastic Film Festival in France, where director Hughes won the Terror Award and was nominated for the jury Grand Prize.
It was theatrically released in France on May 13, 1981, and in the United
Kingdom on July 3, 1981, under its working title, Terror Eyes.
The film subsequently premiered in the United States on
September 11, 1981, distributed by Paramount Pictures.
Night School received mixed reviews from critics, with some praising Hughes's
direction, while others criticized its screenplay and violence.
In the United Kingdom, the film was included on the British Board of Film Classification's list of "video nasties" and
was banned from home video release until 1985, when it was released with over a minute of footage excised.
The film explores themes of chase, ritual, boston,
massachusetts, investigation, college.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.